Hello,
hello friends, welcome to Extra.
Before starting the video, I would like to say a small
thing. Listen, all the
good and popular companies that have
declared their quarterly results date are
available on our channel. If you want, you can watch them
so that you know in advance when your favorite company's quarterly
results are going to come.
And in the future, as good and popular
companies declare their quarterly results date,
we will also quickly
make videos on them so that you can also
get the update quickly. So
friends, let's start today's video and
find out when Dabur's quarterly
results are going to come. Dabur has
filed a notice with the exchanges today.
You can see that notice on your screen right now. It is
clearly written here that a meeting has been fixed by the
company's board of directors on May 5th. It is
written here for whom, you can see it
for the elderly, that is, from here it is clearly
understood that this time the company's
quarterly results will be declared on May 5th.  It's going to be released on 25th May. By the way,
I would like to tell you one thing that
Dabur is a leading company in the egg bhurji sector,
but this time its
quarterly results are going to be very important
because this time the effect of inflation can be
seen in its profit figures.
You must have seen earlier this day that
big companies have increased the prices of their products.
To avoid inflation, these raw materials have become
very expensive. There are many essential
commodities whose prices have increased significantly.
So let's see
how this quarterly results are.
Although its profit will be good, revenue will be
good, but there may be a slight increase,
but this will not ruin the company.
Dabur is no doubt a very good
company, so there is no need to worry. Now take a
look here. There is good
news for Dabur shareholders. The company has
arranged a dividend for its shareholders.
Yes, dividend. But first, the
dividend will be discussed in the board meeting on 5th May.
After discussion, if the dividend is
approved, only then will their
shareholders get the dividend. So
friends, for now  That's all, if you are
new to this channel then keep subscribing to this channel
because
we keep bringing updates related to the share market on this channel,
so we will meet in the next video, till then
goodbye.